{"data":[{"question":"Carelessness is the ___ of the cook's failure.","a":"cause","b":"reason","c":"point","d":"excuse","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Cause: [countable] a person, event, or thing that makes something happen \n+ Cause of \n- Reason: [countable] why someone decides to do something, or the cause or explanation for something that happens \n+ Reason for \n- Point, excuse: the meaning is not suitable","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Many college students support themselves by ___ of finding a part-time job.","a":"means","b":"the way","c":"the help","d":"offer","answer":"1","explain":"- By means of: using a particular method or system","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Some buildings have been pulled down to make ___ for a new park.","a":"place","b":"spaces","c":"land","d":"room","answer":"4","explain":"- Room: space somewhere for a particular thing, person, or activity","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"There are many ___ in her younger brother's drawer.","a":"leafs","b":"mouses","c":"toys","d":"sands","answer":"3","explain":"- Toy-> (plural) toys\n\n- Leaf, mouse, sand-> (plural) leaves, mice, sand","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The university has invented a new kind of ___.","a":"machines","b":"machine","c":"the machine","d":"a machine","answer":"2","explain":"- A new kind of -> singular\n\n- We do not use article to talk about things in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"When she got back, Jennifer was surprised to find _________ broken.","a":"the room's window","b":"the room window","c":"the window of the room","d":"the room of the window","answer":"3","explain":"- The window of the room: give more stress and more specific for both the window and the room (she may notice that window of a room before she left)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Would you please change this ___ note?","a":"ten pounds","b":"ten pound","c":"ten-pounds","d":"ten-pound","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"_________ came that Director Li would drop in on his way here to have ___ with me.","a":"Words; words","b":"The word; a word","c":"Word; a word","d":"Word; the word","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Word came that = There came word that \n+\"Word\" in this example means general information or news \n- Have a word: to talk to someone quickly, especially because you need their advice about something or you want to tell them to do something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The artist's works are better than ___.","a":"anyone else","b":"anyone","c":"anyone's else","d":"anyone else's","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Anyone else's = anyone else's work = work of anyone else","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"We bought many ___ before we moved into the new house.","a":"furniture","b":"furnitures","c":"pieces of furniture","d":"pieces of furnitures","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Furniture is uncoutable noun, we can not say \"many furniture\" in stead we use \" many pieces of\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}